Friend, I am not getting any news, how should I start,
doctor?
[Music]
Malaria symptoms, cheese fever
Please be kind, I am taking loads of crores of medicines,
empty loads, then the one
which is available from the pharmacy
[Music]
Edition open collection, then
you should buy a copy of the monastery, medical
banned generic medicine with D
composition up, you are getting 85% off
in short medicine, the same is not expensive,
your language is diapers, brother, baby
wives, you are laughing,
brother, we have 600, we have
Hero, we have brought a good one, buy it, you must
not have to,
no condom, I am against, this is what happens
[Music]
Chotu, pack it in the wedding bag, friend,
return, follow your speech
[Music]
[Laughter]
Actually, awareness is the bride,
hello ladies and gentlemen, today we will play, so if we become, then we have
given options of ABC, BCC, we have not
only
doctor B,
phone
doctor, somewhere disease option,
quick
medicine,
unfortunately, it is difficult to announce the time limit
[Applause]
[Applause] of the
current  If there was a medicine trending on Instagram last night, if you
want an option, then there are options, right? I
understand what you
want, friend
[Music]
Hey, go ahead, will your
father stop you?
Spend a few days in Gujarat.
Where are the artificial ones? Hey, thank you so much for watching this
video and thank you so much. Generic
medicines in Malaysia, awareness is very
important. If I say it in simple language, then
you are not doing any clothes shopping. You are
asking different brands. You are
buying some coral clothes, some cheap
clothes. But you are going to get your medicines. You
want essential items. Hey, I ask your brandy.
One medicine, not just one
brand, does not cost ₹1000. But
if you ask the wrong pharmacist,
we have generic medicines for you. Those which are
available for ₹200. If I
talk about special medicines, Oho Deepika ji, come come, take
all your medicines, not this, not that,
but you always used to take expensive medicines.
When you get the same name, same quality, same composition at a
lower price, then why would anyone take this?
Whomever you want to share with both of you and who like this video
comment on this video
friends and family and subscribe to D
Comedy Factory you can also join the
membership of Comedy Factory and you can buy
D Comedy Factory Mirch Aate
Creative History dot Store
[Music]